BGM
Here we go... Upokami!
This time we have with us Rika Shimakura of Lyons Subway
and Kanami Ishiguri from Ocha-no-Mama!
This show is about the behind-the-scenes of the production of various artists
This show is about the behind-the-scenes production of the various artists who belong to the Upfront Group.
Our recording, rehearsal, etc.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I, Shimakura, used to use a foam roller to relax my body.
I bought a tool called a foam roller to relax my body.
Recently, I often use the foam roller after a concert or after exercising.
I bought it a long time ago.
I finally started to use it regularly.
I use it before going to bed.
I use it before I go to bed, and I find that I sleep better after I relax my body with the home roller.
I can sleep better and wake up refreshed in the morning.
and I wake up refreshed in the morning.
and my body feels lighter the next day.
I see.
I'm the type of person who can't stick with it for very long.
but I've been doing the home roller for quite a while.
I'm thinking of doing it on a regular basis from now on.
That's good.
I bought a home roller about a year or two ago.
I bought it about a year or two ago, but it's really just an ornament.
I can't use it at all.
I'd like to learn from you and do my best.
And I, Ishifuri...
I've been performing at Hello Project concerts in the summer.
I'd like to talk a little about the costume of the new song "Chihaya-buru, the Tea Horse" which is performed at the Hello Project concert in the summer.
The costume is based on red and white color.
It has no arms.
It's a sleeveless costume.
It's a sleeveless costume, so it's a costume that shows off my arms and stuff.
I like that my arms are flabby.
That's nice.
I had a complex about it, so in the time between the costume and the music video shoot, I worked really hard on my arms every day, and for the first time in a long time, I was able to do something to keep them in shape,
I've been slacking off a bit lately, but I'd like to take this opportunity to start working hard again from today.
I'd like to take this opportunity to work hard again today.
Let's start with the first one.
Angelem's Vivitar One-Shot Dance Lesson
Here's a look at the dance lesson for Vivitar Ichigeki from Angelem's latest single!
Let's go from before that.
You know, before the tulou's before that.
So what was it from before that?
Before that.
Se-no.
Yes, sir.
Oh, you can do it.
Here you go.
I can do it.
Here you go, Ma-chan.
I don't dance.
Yes, ma'am.
I won't dance.
I won't dance, I won't dance, I won't dance, I won't dance, I won't dance, I won't dance
Jingle, jingle, jingle, jingle, jingle, jingle
I'll love you to the end of the chorus
I'll love you
Chirihin
Southern
nload
Treatment
Why a little guide
6 out sometime
Thank you very much.
I didn't see any number 8.
I got the number 8.
The usual.
Why are you being so modest?
It's okay.
It's okay, you can stay in here.
You sure about that? Let me see it again.
I'll make sure you do it that way.
One more time. One more time.
Ready?
I'm gonna make love to you.
That's what I'm talking about.
Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara
Tara Tara Tara Tara Tara Tara
Then Rancha Rancha Rancha Rancha
Oh, excuse me
If you go, you have to come here
If you go, your hand has to come here
Once here
Once you come here
There you go.
Okay, is it here?
Okay, okay.
Can I move?
Let's go again.
Come with me.
I love you.
Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara, Tara.
Can you go?
Yes, I'm good.
Okay, okay.
Here, in front.
Oh, this one?
Oh, there's one who raises his hand after this.
Some of you are raising your hands after this, and some of you are raising your hands after that, and some of you are raising your hands after this.
Uh...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Maybe he's raising it from here.
Let's do feet and hands together.
Yes, sir.
That's right.
Let's leave the hands on and do one shot here.
Yes, yes, yes.
At this time,
You have a lot of questions.
There are a lot of them.
Do you want to face forward or sideways?
I'll turn to the side.
Yes, look sideways for a moment.
Chut-chut-chut-chut-chut-chut-chut-chut-chut-chut-chut.
Thank you very much.
Now, come on, come on.
When and when?
All day.
Let's do this.
All days
Here's one.
And the rest?
There's so much more.
I'm gonna bring my front foot up, and I'm gonna go from behind.
Where's the move?
Before that.
Number two.
Keep it closed.
Now this leg.
Back.
Okay, I'll take it.
Okay, what about the rest?
Let's go!
Engine! Engine!
Engine! Engines!
Interval!
Yeah!
Three minutes, one minute, three minutes, one minute.
Let's go for it, people.
Okay, what'll it be?
Let's go.
Let's go for it.
Keep it up and smile, right?
Let's go with smiley face.
Let's go for it!
Kitty & Smart
Let's go!
Stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay
OK!
Okay, one minute!
Let's go!
Five seconds!
Yes!
Four, three, two, one.
Let's go!
Tia, up here, Tia!
Tia, come here!
Ei, ei, yah, ei, yah, ei, yah, ei, yah,
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah...
Masher, masher!
Stay, stay, stay,
OK!
I'm not strong enough.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Three, two, one.
One.
Yes, sir.
Let's do number one.
Nice.
Next one's not just a piece of cake.
I'm the king.
Yes, sir.
Such a mouth
That mouth.
It hasn't changed
My sparkles.
Yes, sir.
You can never have too much of it.
Mariful
Yes, ma'am.
Make sure it's regulated.
All of them next time.
Someday that should change.
The day before glory.
Yes, sir.
You're not done yet.
You're a good girl now, aren't you?
Yes, ma'am.
One.
Two.
Three. - Four.
Four. - Four.
thank you for all your hard work
I love you.
Yeah!
I'm a Easy is Easy is Easy is Easy
Thanks for your time
Ryudo guest seems
Year
Yes, I have finished the choreography of VIVITAL Ichigeki.
This song has the word "ichigeki" in it, and there are a lot of choreographies of the 10 movements in this song,
We were moving all the time and there was no time to take a break, so we just kept dancing from the beginning to the end,
The song is about 4 minutes long, and everyone dances for about 4 minutes,
We danced, took a minute break, danced again, took a break, and repeated the practice three times.
Everyone was really exhausted at the end.
But by doing this interval
But by doing these intervals, we gradually came to understand that it was cooler to relax here and there.
I think it's a very important way to practice.
I think this is a very important way to practice.
The highlight of this song is the interlude when everyone is dancing and everyone is kicking in the front.
The part where they kick in front of the audience is really cool, so I hope you pay attention to that part.
Yes, it's a coup. I saw the dance lesson,
I was surprised to see the difference between BEYOND's choreography and Angstrom's choreography.
Overall? The atmosphere was like a real performance?
The teacher was really excited. I thought it was a great atmosphere. It was really cool.
I like the song "Vivitar Ichigeki" very much, and of course I like the song, but I was really paying attention to the dance,
So to be able to see the video of the dance lesson like this was very valuable.
There are a lot of intense but also very detailed movements, and I think it is a song that really requires a lot of physical strength, but I have seen it performed so coolly at live performances,
I'm looking forward to seeing this song getting cooler and cooler from now on.
That's all for now, this is the dance lesson of Angstrom Vivitar.
Thank you for watching.
Angellum Vivitar Ichigeki Now on SIRYO
Let's work together!
Here is the next one
BEYOND'S Hook's Law Vocal Recording
Law of Hook from BEYOND'S latest single
Here's a look at Minami Okamura's vocal recording
Yes, yes, well, we'll take it block by block.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes
Let's go ahead and organize
I want to protect my heart I want to be strong I want that kind of strength
I've been shrinking back, my true wish, because I've been confiding in you.
Great. If we keep it a little longer and change the way you sing it, a little cooler, a little more mature, can you try it one more time?
I'm sorry, I don't know why I loaded it up at the end.
I want to protect my heart.
I want to be strong.
A true wish
I've been confiding in you
Seiten
Yeah, let's do this.
I've made up my mind, I'm going with this.
Okay, I got it.
Let's go to B melody, shall we?
Yes, sir.
Shrinking down
A true wish
Keep
I was confiding in you
Holy electricity
Dance, dance, dance, dance
With you and you
With you, sometimes alone
With completion
Bye bye bye bye
Use your failures as a springboard
Yeah, a little more, maybe with a thicker voice. As much as possible, without being scared.
And, you know, the karaoke arrangement says "dance dance dance dance, dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens dens
Dansei detsutta keton, dens dens dens dens, with you and you and you, toki toki hit, dance dance dance dance next time.
I'd like to put "bye bye, bye bye, use your failure as a springboard".
I'd like to add a little more nuance to the "spring it up" part.
Sometimes alone with
To completion
Bye bye bye!
Failure is also a springboard.
I think it's good.
Let's do the chorus
I'll do the rust and pull your hand into the future that no one knows
Epicolour case
KX, can't you just use your own voice?
If we call KX GO!
Stronger there too in a series. I don't care if it's a little bit low, but I think it should be strong. At the end.
The other thing I just noticed is the first line.
I want to increase the power of the first line. A little more rhythmic.
After that, I want to unleash the power of the dream. A little more firm.
Yes.
At the end, you want to go to blue with your own voice.
Yes, sir.
A little bit high.
I think it'll probably be okay.
Let's try it once.
To completion, bye-bye every time Failure can be a springboard
Let's go, let's go, let's go Let's go, let's go
Be your, be your, be your, be yourself
Jump up, jump up, jump up, jump up, jump up, jump up, jump up, jump up, jump up, jump up, jump up, jump up
I want to unleash the power I've decided Let's go!
Be your, be your, be your, be your, be yourself
I'll dye and pull you into the future that no one knows
Effikolkix!
OK!
OK, that's good!
Okay, back to the head, two lines on the theme.
That's it! Extension extension?
Let's sing a little harder.
Extension. It tends to sound a little bit like tension.
So let's make it tension. Okay, let's go one more time.
Extension. So explore!
OK, that was perfect. Okay, next rap!
Because of the dream, the tight review that is always in balance
Invisible power as a formula Bouncing rhythms in the club
Come on F equals KX
Say F equals KX
Bounce!
Spring up!
Bounce! Bounce! Bounce! Bounce!
And also, your voice is a little lower and thicker.
Let's give it one more try to make it look cooler!
Now for take two.
Let's do BFB because of our dreams
Always in balance, always on equal footing
I can't see the invisible force and I can't see you
Hazmovie the club in the mood
Come on!
Say F.E.C.O.L.K.X.
Bose!
Spring up!
OK, so it's over with no difficulty.
Oh, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Yes, this song is from the BEYOND study series,
Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler, a song about the mathematics of the mountain,
This time it's a song about the Hooke's law of physics,
The theme of this song is about the laws of physics, and the beginning of the song is a line of dialogue.
At first I had the impression that the song was a bit comical, a bit like Beyoncé, but when I listened to the music more closely, I found it to be very cool.
But when I listened to the music more carefully, I found that it was really cool, and the beat was really chugging.
The way the members sang along with it made it a really cool song.
Especially now that I saw Okamura Minami, she always looks so cute.
Yes.
So when I heard Mimi's singing voice for the first time after this song was written, I thought it was really cool.
The first part of the A melody is sung by Minami Okamura and Momohime Seino.
I love the phrasing of their singing, it's so cool!
So I hope you'll see it at the live performance.
Yes, Mimmy is really cool.
I think she's cool and stylish at the same time.
I could see a lot of fine techniques and so on.
I was so fascinated by it, I couldn't stop listening to it.
It was such a wonderful recording video that I listened to it intently.
I was able to witness the live viewing of Yohane Yamazaki's graduation concert.
I was able to observe her graduation concert through live viewing.
I think she performed this song at the concert.
I actually went back to see the music video when I heard it.
Wow!
I thought it was a really cool song, and I'd like to see more of it at live shows.
That's all for Beyonce's Hook's Law, Minami Okamura's vocal recording.
Keep smiling and good things will happen!
This is Apkami with Rika Shimakura from Beyonce's Subway and Kanami Ishiguri from Ocha-no-Ma.
Here's the next one!
JuiceJuice Tokyo Blur Vocal Recording
Here's a look at the vocal recording of Tokyo Blur Kisaki Ebata from JuiceJuice's latest single!
Okay, let's do it.
Please do.
First, M Rock.
Anciteru car con afreso.
Let's try it up to here.
I'm fine, grid.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
I don't love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you...
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I'm overflowing tonight.
I'll make it a little longer.
This is totally unrelated, but...
What is that thing in your left hand?
It's a pen.
Is it a flower?
I was wondering what you were holding.
I was going to write.
That's what I thought.
Okay, let's go one more time.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
I don't love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
Radio to brass, rain in the forecast.
Okay.
Let's do it.
I don't love you, I love you, I love you, Tokyo, it's gonna pour tonight.
Radio announces rain forecast.
I'm not at work, so why are you depressed?
Lady O, galaboo.
This is the length of the note.
Lady-o, galaboo.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Lady O' Garaboo
Tomorrow
So far, all at the same time.
like this
And then I'll cut it off.
Yes, sir.
Let's give it a good try.
You're not working, why are you so depressed?
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's gay, it's gay, it's gay, it's gay, it's gay, it's gay
It's the part before the chorus, right?
I can't leave him alone!
I can't leave him alone, he's so weak
I can't leave him alone, he's so weak, but he's got a story to tell, a story to tell.
At the next corner
Yes, OK, isn't it good?
Okay, let's try the first chorus
Demp tension squeak
You can say it like this, or you can say it in the middle.
Let's go with it.
Here we go...
Graduation, the hair is gently slicked back, wind.
Yes, yes, that's what I mean, that's what I mean. It's OK like this.
Let's see,
Tempten.
Here. Go ahead and change it.
Is there something you want me to play first?
Go ahead and change it.
I don't know how to say it...
Come and change it... and it sinks.
That part...
The way the "de" sounds.
So that it doesn't get muddy
Come and get it
It's like a little bit shiny.
I wish I could do that.
Go ahead and change it.
The hand that takes
of sleepless love
Get out of your lodgings
With a new me
Let's go see a new morning
Graduation
The wind is gently blowing my hair back
OK
Yes, sir.
Here you go.
Okay, let's see.
Rusty.
Let's go to the chorus.
Temptation, Korshiyoki no Love & Jai, here you go, change it up
Take the wheel, sleepless love, down in the air
Good-bye, my heart is so clear, I'll never get it back, but...
But, hey, Tokyo, beyond the tears, my head and I are feeling great.
a...come here...here...it's going to get lower and lower...so let's make him notice a little more...so let's take away the handle of sleepless love...
Get off the spine and go to Coconner's place!
I think I'm a little short right now, Taku-chan.
And wait.
But, you know, a little bit, it's a little bit oozing behind the tears.
But, you know, a little bit of a smile behind the tears.
But, but just a little bit.
And then, before the next tear, she stops for a moment,
I want a pause before the next tear.
Then, cut off the head of the tear,
And then, I cut the head of the tear, and the tear oozes out.
Then, let's try one more time.
And let's try one more time.
Temptation Sokusayoki no Love & Joy
Here, come back to me
Handle to take, sleepless love
Down the tree line
Goodbye, my heart
So clear, there's no going back
But you know what? Beyond the tears...
Blotchy Tokyo
I've almost got it, but this is the only part I really need to work on.
I'm thinking it would be better if I could come out a little stronger there.
Temptation Yoyoyoki no Love & Joy
Here, I changed it.
I think it's OK. Well, I guess that's all. Thank you very much for your hard work. Thank you very much.
Yes, I saw Kisaki Ebata's decoding.
I saw how she sang each phrase with great care, and I thought her singing style was wonderful.
I also thought that she sings in a very mature way.
But when Mr. Taisei was listening to you, his face looked like a baby's.
It was the seriousness of an older woman, wasn't it?
I thought it was so cute to see Kisaki in such a serious mood.
I was surprised at your sense of rhythm.
I always thought you were really good at rhythm when I watched your performances.
But in your current vocal recording, you sang all the phrases without losing the rhythm.
I want to refer to your voice so much because it's so mature.
I also want to be able to have a sense of rhythm and be able to sing cool songs with it.
That's all for JuiceJuice Tokyo Blur and Kisaki Ebata's vocal recording.
Take care of yourself and don't push yourself too hard!
It's time to say goodbye to Rika Shimakura and Kanami Ishigiri!
Now, we have seen various videos this time.
First of all, I, Ishigiri, was impressed by the video of Ms. Angelou's "Vivitar Ichigeki" dance lesson.
I love and admire Rikako Sasaki, and there are many scenes of her dancing in the middle of the song.
I wondered if someone else would be dancing in that spot in the future.
I was also very curious about the scene of her impression.
Even during the rehearsal
The atmosphere of the team, including the teacher, was wonderful.
I wish I could give lessons like that at Ocha-no-Ma, and I learned a lot.
I, Shimakura, was very impressed with Okamura Minami's vocal recording of Hook's Law.
We've performed together and done a lot of live performances, but I think I like Okamura Minami's A-melody part the best.
I was able to see the vocal recording and hear Okamura Minami's cool voice in all of it, which was a new experience for me at this song.
I was able to see and hear all of Okamura Minami's cool voice, and I'm really looking forward to seeing the new
I think there are many scenes in this song that showcase the new Minami Okamura, so I want to continue to pay attention to her performance and work hard with her.
In this issue of APKAMI, we will go behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UPFRONT GROUP.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't usually get to see. This time on Apkami, we have Rika Shimakura from BEYONES Subway and Kanami Ishigiri from Ocha no Ma!
Good bye.
Next time on Apkami, we have a dance lesson with BEYONES GO CITY GO!
And
We will be showing you the recording of Angeleum's rumored Narcissy!
Please look forward to it!